the brain is the most fascinating part
of the human body not much to look at it
resembles a spongy massive tissue feels
like tofu and weighs roughly four tubs
of
butter our brain is actually made up of
mostly water and about 10%
fats while our brain only makes up
approximately 2% of the entire body's
weight it uses a massive 20% of the
body's
energy the brain's basic building blocks
are known as neurons and we have around
100 billion of these each with between
1,000 to 10,000 connections to other
neurons creating neural Pathways or
roads within the brain there are
literally trillions of neural
connections within the brain similar to
a city's electrical power grid
information is passed along these roads
through a series of chemical messages
and electrical impulses
as all of this activity takes place our
brain generates between 10 to 25 watts
of power enough to power a light bulb
over the course of one day your brain
generates more electrical impulses from
firing neurons than all of the
telephones in the world so really your
brain isn't just a spongy mass of tissue
it's your most complex organ a power
station that connects your every thought
movement and feeling and it's barring
right now